Kytcat - Database

-Fields are columns headings 
    >True

-What is usually the first step in the design process of a database?
   >collect information

-Which operation can't we perform on a database using DDL?
   >INSERT

-Which statement is true?
   >A foreign key references a primary key in another table.

-Records are rows of a table
  >True

-Which architecture is the most widely used to design a DBMS?

  >3-tier

-Marerialized views increase performance 
  >True

-What are the two main purposes of normalization?
  >Ensuring data dependencies make sense
  >Eliminating redundant data

-How do you carry out a SQL injection?
  >by using special characters in your request.

-Simply put, what is the entire purpose of a database?
  >to store and manage data

-RDBMS can be pictured like an organized library 
  >True

-SQL is a language
  >True

-Each table of a database has only one foreign key
  >False

-Some tables of a database may not have a primary key
  >False

-What is an advantage of NoSQL upon SQL?
  >flexibility

-What is the purpose of ER-diagrams?
  >to illustrate logical structure of databases

-Which choice contains some usual SQL commands?
  >SELECT, INSERT, DROP, DELETE

-What are frequent if a database is not normalized?
  >anomalies

-ACID stands for:
  >Atomicity, Consistency, Isolation, Durability

-I need to store data in a database with many relations. I'll choose a DBMS with;
  >SQL

-Each table of a database has at least one primary key
  >False

-There isn't open-source DBMS.
  >False

-I want to migrate my database from NoSQL to SQL. What must I do to have a functional database?
  > Query syntax is different, I must update the database's queries.

-ORM is another language, like SQL, used to communicate with a database.
  >False

-SQL injections are not possible with postgreSQL.
  >False

-Which command is used to add data in a database?
  >INSERT

-Which one is not a function of DBMS?
  >it duplicates data

-Who is widely considered the father of relational database design?
  >Edgar F. CODD

-Which statement is true:
  >Tables are made of rows and columns

-Which operation can't we perform on a database using DML?
  >SELECT

-Choose 2 DCL-operations:
  >GRANT
  >REVOKE

-What is the usual name for the return of a query?
  >The result

-To improve your database's security, you can:
  > use encryption


-I have a 'users' table and a 'roles' table. Each user can have several ples. In order to associate users to roles, I will:
  > create a pivot table which associates a user ID and a role ID


-Choose 4 DML-operations
  >DELETE, INSERT, UPDATE, SELECT


-Which one is not a common database data type?
  >record

-How can you ensure data quality, accuracy and completeness?
  >using constraints


-need to store data with a different structure. I'll choose:
  >NOSQL


-What is useful to improve the availability of data?
  >data replication


-Which one is a primary key constraint?
  >uniqueness


-I have a 'users' table and a 'roles' table. Each user can have only one role. In order to associate a role to a user, I will:
  >Add a 'role' column in the 'users' table and store role' id